Where are we going?   We're
going to JP Morgan to see the
stock opening.  It is a moment that occurs only
once in the history of an
action.  So there will be a guy
called Stabilization Agent who on the
phone like in the movies, he is the entire
trading desk, they call buyers,
sellers, how many shares, at what price and
they try to match supply and demand to
ensure that the first trade starts and from there
everything is automatic.  Keep in mind that
the document you send to the SEC alone,
which everyone can read when it
's finally ready, is about 400 pages
plus hundreds of pages of attachments, and
you have to weigh every line because there are
legal implications, it can have an
impact on the market's perception of the
company, but that's just
the tip of the iceberg.  There are 1000
policies that you have to develop because as a
listed company you have to have a policy
for a lot of things that before I'm not saying
you cared about, but you could have managed them a
little more as they came.
We had to expand the board because there
are more stringent requirements,
prepare presentations, hold meetings.
Over the past month, we've reportedly spoken to over
100 investors, some two or three
times.